{
    "subject": "resource/Efrat",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Israel",
    "human_readable": "Efrat is located in Israel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8585116267204285,
            "question": "Where is Efrat located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.634698212146759,
            "question": "What country is Efrat in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4464733898639679,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks near Efrat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3963950276374817,
            "question": "Is Efrat a town or a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3564983308315277,
            "question": "What is the history of Efrat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34598132967948914,
            "question": "Is Efrat a popular tourist destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.334909051656723,
            "question": "What are some cultural attractions in Efrat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32173246145248413,
            "question": "What is the population of Efrat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24778498709201813,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Efrat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1961642950773239,
            "question": "Can you name a city in Israel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Efrat is located in Israel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6731_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Efrat?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6731_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Efrat?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6731_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some cultural attractions in Efrat?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6731_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6731_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6731_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6731_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6731_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6731_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6731_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6731_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6731_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6731_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6731_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information that supports the triple \"Efrat is located in Israel\". The documents state that Efrat is an Israeli settlement, and its location is specified as being in the Judean Mountains of the West Bank, south of Jerusalem, between Bethlehem and Hebron. This suggests that Efrat is indeed located in Israel, specifically in the West Bank."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents repeatedly mention that Efrat is an Israeli settlement, established and located within the West Bank. This supports the statement that Efrat is located in Israel."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}